RODRIGO LOPEZ RAZO

Full Stack Developer Lead

Full Stack software developer with about 12 years experience on backend and frontend development. Across my experience as developer I have developed a high sense of urgency, I have worked for companies where it is necessary to solve an issue in minutes, this has led me to have a great experience with errors or problems in production. I like to be updated with the new technologies for web applications or mobile applications. Currently I'm as leader of multicultural team. I always try to have a good communication with team to reach the objectives of project.

| EDUCATION

Universidad de la salle Bajio (2005 - 2009) Computer and systems engineering

WORKING EXPERIENCES

M6Connect (December 2022– Present day)

Sr. Full Stack Developer Lead

Technology Stack: Vuejs, Spring Boot Java, Typescript, Google GCP , Javascript

Project: Video Game Element United (https://www.elementunited.com/)

Project Description: Video Game on web for crypto

- Development of platform front end for the video game
- Create the API on spring boot

M6Connect (Oct 2020 – December 2022)

Sr. Full Stack Developer Lead

Technology Stack: Vuejs, Laravel, Lumen, NodeJs, AWS (S3,Lambda Functions), Javascript

Project: M6 Platform

Project Description: Develop of process-oriented platform for hospitals:

- Development of platform developers.m6connect.com
- Create components for specific functionality on platform as ex. Feed as Facebook/Twitter/Linkedin
- Development and implementation of Restful Web APIs, and exposes endpoints using HTTP verbs like GET, PUT,
 POST and DELETE with nodejs/Laravel/lumen
- Deploys and Pull request review on Git hub
- Taking of requirements
- Leader of Developers and manage the team.

All projects where under git version control

Instituto Lux (OCt 2014 – Oct 2020)

I Software Developer Lead

Technology Stack: .Net, Vue.js, SQL, HTML5, Javascript

- Development Web Application for Register of new members(made With VueJS +
- Laravel) https://lux.org.mx/admisiones/#/
- Develoment Web Application to Instituto Lux College for Child delivery (intranet)
- made with VueJs + Laravel
- Development of the current landing page (php-mysql, responsive) with panel http://institutolux.edu.mx
- administration.
- Development of help desk for tickets support (php-mysql)
- Development of application for rating capture BADyG's evaluation (C# MCV)
- Improvement and administration of the school's web and office control system
- Improvement and administration of the institute's cash control system.
- Administration of domain and mail of the institute (platform google).

Siemens (Apr. 2014 –Oct 2014)

I Sr. Software Developer

Technology Stack: .Net, asp.net, SQL, DevExpress

• Web application development for the administration of computer equipment (Register, Low, Reservation, Assignment of equipment) developed in C #, SQL Server 2008, WCF)

Calzado Andrea (Aug. 2012 – Apr. 2014)

I Sr. Software Developer

Technology Stack: .Net, asp.net, SQL, DevExpress

- Development of WCF Services for sending e-mail to Andrea
- System Customers.
- Development of WCF Services for billing through a Supplier's DLL (MySuite).
- Development and improvements to the sales system.

Poder Judicial del Estado de Guanajuato (March. 2009 –Aug. 2012)

I Webmaster

Technology Stack: .Net, asp.net, SQL, Mysql, PHP, C#, WCF

- Updating of the page design of www.poderjudicial-gto.gob.mx (Years of update:2009,
- 2011, 2012)
- Development of a portal for mobile devices for the consultation of court recordsand
- Chambers.
- Improvement in the publication of Court Agreements for consultation from the
- website.
- New service for the Consultation of Edicts from the portal.
- New Service to display the index of the digitized file.
- New Service for the printing of data sheet for stagecoaches.
- New virtual Platform for the internal and external use with technology Asp.Net, WCF, Jquery.
- Mantenaince & backup database

| SKILLS

Operating systems: MS-Windows, Centos 7

Backend Development: Spring Boot Java, NodeJS, Laravel, Lumen, .NET C# WCF

Frontend Development: VueJS, React, React Native

Databases: MySQL, SQL Server

Tools and platforms: AWS, GCP

| LANGUAGES

Spanish (Native)

English (Professional Proficiency)